I hope the quality is good because the
stabilizer is so sick
oh but I'm not really understanding
having you
yes
cake icing like rotated like
[Music]
pretty cool right
thanks for the great Spanish reminder
you're surely welcome Oh
oh yeah we've got 42 this is this is not
YouTube live yeah what missus Bible in
Portuguese - what you're using the most
creative language shout-out to him I
like the new white shirt says here thank
you do people like periscope again is it
okay for YouTube why I think it's just
like way worse quality but it's like
it's all we have like we don't to give
all of our information
and like no one gets alert while any
good you all really pretty girls
wait-wait-wait
we're in the vaccine
to Mesa Arizona yeah
- Mason we dismiss you - blood for one
session because we got complaints of
periscope but then it was like just
really different
but then periscope with soaps that we
left that they improve the quality
that's right
periscope contacted us so thank you guys
for apps we're back
you just have to subscribe on youtube I
never does a lot to ask people to
subscribe to YouTube and like Obama's
really into pairs go for some reasons
like what do we call the people that
watch YouTube live sorry
liars hey developers sure yeah
they on yeah Harold has a new scheme for
creating generally oh there's the police
patrol oh we just saw a car that was on
fire you guys
we have lemon city know
oh yeah it sort of leads Tomas Tomas
knows we're coming from Burbank school
we sold a lot of sorry see that the
profit is a few Blake destabilize for
one second and freaks out why does it do
it's some unstable control
you think they use MPC how come doesn't
drift I'd understand doesn't treat why
would it truth going on my free silver
pilots name bracelet Pacifica awesome we
hope you enjoy it
oops sorry do you guys hope to get out
of your visit to heatsink tomorrow
what's a good question that's the
makerspace is called Itza yeah
what are you get out of it we're gonna
just present up over two weeks we're
gonna have a mobile shoe store for you
guys we also want to see Mesa Arizona
never been if you have any heat sinks
we'll fix it
we're also trying to go see some wheat
Mo's when we're there you know say hi to
our fellow friends yeah we're gonna
track down some wave over in Jackson
there's cars happening we working on we
thought those a panda somebody's
complaining about the cables being
untidy I agree this yeah see I'm so
sorry
what was the where the Hyundai so like
the giraffe sticks out this way
you know any guys really well
mr. bast yeah well that
my god something's happened
funny oh my god it's fighting back
someone hacked our TGI stabilizer DGI I
think like okay I let it go it's gonna
go he's a big dater probably you can't
fight it turn it off and on again
okay so I guess it does it changes in
the joystick mode where you can pins
okay
great
what else
what does anyone have any dinner
recommendations on the later
oh shoot I just flipped the cave this is
so terrible I'm sorry and I don't I
don't know I have to switch it back yeah
we've had technical problems I'm just
trying to reflect those
oK we've experienced technical problems
our monkeys are working well what's but
the problem is that this stabilizers are
no longer works I've like literally lost
like half the viewers I'm just gonna
have to hold it because that was like
really really dick you we have 34 we
have 45 yeah
pre use most part Isaac how may I open
source Chris black these cars are so
amazing because we have like a full moon
roof back here they say oh we played the
alphabet game yeah there's this game
where you try and find the letter of the
alphabet
if we sold final yeah we should sell
decals because people would put them on
their car and then we didn't own the
alphabet game has a Wikipedia page
really it's just called alphabet game as
called the Alpha the alphabet game is a
card game played to amuse travelers on
long car rides soundtrack version is on
the one we're driving final seven
Thank You Beth yeah we got three or five
seven
should do a comment ama yeah I mean you
can always say don't put any kind of
sticker on my car but I would totally
put a comment so good oh hey secret good
version I'm gonna cover Magnus you know
you can put a sticker on your laptop or
your phone oh it's a Monday no say
Saturday
why what's happening orders ship out
Saturday Monday last night yeah that's
our last day of shipping if you want
something before Christmas order it
today understand what we want from
perhaps is they really the first
question it's not obvious like everybody
don't supportive demands like if there
was like clear definition what a man is
maps are clear how you define lower
swoosh of maps like Google Maps Apple
maps they will do the same thing right
it's clear and what information you want
from them the HD match is not obvious
they really depends on which kind of you
wanna do with them
and so we really like try to understand
that what's going to be useful for the
pilot right so well yeah and so that's I
would say the main F for the last week
was very clear with that then we have
the data we just have to do it is the
this latest version on yeah yeah so you
have to switch to develop branch if you
want to be like that like our tester
yeah thank you for coming to the meetup
in Burbank we had fun Burbank's a cool
place except for I was told that it's
not cool to sleep every school really
got doughnuts in Burbank
she's all my Tech's come up on here
that's so sketchy
it is my god I don't want them apple
carplay sucks ready I'll read your text
are we gonna check that Tempe maybe
we're getting in at like 11:00 p.m. so
we gotta figure out the traffic Toyota
will totally be on sale at the data
store yeah absolutely we'll have some
with us
and apple carplay is bad like you can't
use your phone at all if you take if I
try and use another app we can mash goes
away so embarrassing like and I can only
use these few things I can use Google
[Music]
Brannigan make it brandon has city with
don't worry quality so bad we will do
side-by-side comparison we'll do both
yeah we'll do YouTube live tomorrow yeah
QA about the car face if only we knew
someone that could jailbreak
no I was talking about this with with
Andrew like I can't believe Apple even
lens like this is the only place that
you can run something like something
from Apple on non-apple harder yeah like
I'm surprised they give up the
experience it's like it's the only place
they really do that the next time they
don't be sure how it works and like it's
not good it's so much better but I'd
rather have a good phone mount that like
just went there than any kind of carplay
the screen is like barely bigger than
mine
I love Android auto seems better cuz you
can like switch between
just a good amount
right yeah it's like no point
I can only use that format
and like all my music is being displayed
to people we listen to a good podcast
yesterday by Lex Friedman for the expert
did you figure it out you know but I
didn't realize you can spin it there's
pretty Funko in a different mode I'm
like spin it it's kind of fun I think
it's good rigs most exercise that's
super unstable let's put the scobie's in
that
we got 4 hours and 44 minutes
to the table table city
it's pretty easy
speed limit apple says 55 we say 60
right right check 65 right off we can go
now it's three lanes it's gotta be 65
yeah
[Music]
we get our data from spoken stream app
there's another chick-fil-a
we should get we should get a milkshake
at some point tonight yeah
I guess would be gonna be ashame yeah
love milkshakes they do an ice cream
stop hu before did it yeah you're gonna
ruin your appetite
like don't articulate real chicken - oh
what's gonna make an sheykh stock on a
GPS it also displays speed limit
obvious bath
next
but people ask you we have a new secret
heart over yeah because I'm do anything
he just sits in the basement
and just like come up with new names for
your ass
it makes cool keychains oh yeah the
keychains look good anyone out there has
it she see this is where it gets like so
bumpy I mean having the stabilizer
explained Matt I did it work
it's just you know I don't know I don't
want to put them in and then smash out
again
has to buy a historical district I don't
know what goes on
hey very personally Chris how's it going
yeah we're in the Hyundai it's going
well it drives super nice so just like
love in the back this thing is equipped
for children like you'll have a warning
when you open the door that make sure
you know you didn't leave your child in
the backseat it's a truly phenomenal
family Ricardo cute every one of us in
this they both say 65
[Music]
you're pretty slow to talk you do we
have 40 is that a lot so it's something
that's so like the 40 miles my heart
Fortuna then there's snow on these
mountains on the left yeah yes you
didn't really miss much virtually Chris
we kind of just have been doing this the
whole time just chat
been driving
we want the scope before the Sun went
down lighting Otto
well you guys know that we're gonna look
for huevos for you you know we're gonna
make sure they're safe like maybe Eddie
you consider the front of one and just
make sure it stops baby chemistro at all
are we gonna do some live coding in the
car
good what do you want live code yeah
I'll do some live coding and
[Music]
you could do like lying with your life
that's fun
snake in Python is a game snake I had to
do that for my introductory yeah it was
fun
hoping next step now that doesn't sound
as fun a snake hello world in CSS I feel
like that's someone's like College and
we're like on the brink of doing it
really yeah yeah that's good I was
interested at snake I mean I think thing
could be a good YouTube channel coding
in the car the car would it be good
Eddie
no they said oh don't make that
I think we can make something in the car
you can make it work you mean yeah I
don't know I don't know how to make
gooeys in Python
I thought you use like my game all the
time to build the deal you're going to
really hide nothing how about my octo
map integration is super awesome
just saying
slows down yes without four curves are
you real not yet
but
it says
let's import this group is like into our
yeah yeah no yeah we can keep going with
like oh yeah the debate we had yesterday
night yeah a stethoscope is what you
guys speak about consciousness and
intelligence do you believe there can be
consciousness without intelligence or
intelligence without consciousness
what business without until our
intelligence without conscious
conscience
they did put together like are they
linked they need
are you guys saying I don't think they
need to be like no identifying
consciousness in the podcast fi yeah
that you Dante we see the young gets
driving data consciousness less and how
it is update what does that mean so I
wrote consciousness let's intelligence
update itself
are you defining consciousness
consciousness update teachers updating
self
like eons have experiences right like
they they have like a route that's what
we call them that's what they're
experiencing I suppose they have no
subjective experience right they have no
notion of self it knows it till the eco
and another one plus tau zero one open
pilot oh it's flat okay no some
arbitrary notify something does it like
you can't it can't communicate in any
way just how does that have to do with
inexperience the communication part
super no I mean it it doesn't know what
its limitations are and what its body is
and we know that because it can't
communicate that any way like it I guess
it isn't necessarily what do you mean it
just can't communicate but if they know
or you la dia might have subjective
experience but we just don't know
because it can't tell us
you might have a very rough form of
subjective experience like the thingies
so clearly like I have subjective
experience I think I don't know about
you guys but I assume that you guys had
me do because you seem very much like I
am right but at the same time I conceive
of things not having subjective
experience and being intelligence right
so you can create that you can put
together molecules and create an
intelligent creature so he says the
state of being awake and aware of one's
surroundings
yeah I don't know it has to be more
strict than that right limit the
findings should never feel bad about how
we treat computers yeah is it like what
you guys think should we have a field
band on now between computers
killing robots here named Robert killing
a robot that's what you're saying yeah I
mean badly even a dignity we were all
but you can ever dignity that we have to
care about
the best the best from the podcast is
how who wasn't that max the professor's
there wasn't lek so say you didn't want
to be carbon chauvinistic which is like
goodbye Carbon chauvinistic looking very
lion especially in the future we live in
them
we're like you don't necessarily need to
be Parvin based to be saying that I got
not a carbon chauvinist pig I think
anything could have an experience that
was like a dog has experience right does
a fly have experience yeah but there's a
bacteria
because the form of intelligence left in
your system is like just because there's
less intelligent way but you'd say a fly
has subjective experience well if they
can't express like the dog we have some
part of the communication that you can
express with each other even if you
cannot express it doesn't mean perceived
is expressing yourself is not an issue
speculation to be intelligent to or to
add subjective experience but that
depends on how you define subjective
experience
I mean consciousness Ryan conscious is
your subjective experience thank you Dad
I don't know it's very hard to define
but India that basically you perceive
that's the very definition of subjective
is that it doesn't define but like
whatever is going on that we Tina's Safi
that is gonna have been too intelligent
for but it's gonna be the future like a
computer yeah yeah that's seems
reasonable I mean I was listening to
some research that they find
consciousness that's like the ability to
realize that you are one entity until
ability to understand your own
perspective and realize that other
entities have different perspectives and
so I kind of know that you have you're
like this one entity with a place in the
world and that other entities have a
similar subjective point of view that's
different but isn't that all part of
what you could define an intelligent
system like this seems like
we might have very good definition about
intelligence and everything that you can
say about the definition of
consciousness actually seems just really
apply to intelligence and doesn't
clearly define well but this is why some
some researchers also claim that
consciousness isn't a thing right like
Daniel Dennett is one of those things
that says I mean consciousness just
doesn't feel like people should stop
talking about it
well that may be that make sense right
but why do we care about defining any
ethics right consciousness and the fear
of hurting other people for imagining an
alternative like you could be earth is
what what's making us defining like
maybe x-ray but holding on to the idea
of consciousness just so you can have
ethics so you don't die is if this
sounds like
and enough that that's in Portugal
like you shouldn't hold on to
consciousness so just so that you can
create ethics like ethics wouldn't be
justified if I'm actually convinced that
other end it is probably older than me
or video/dvd knows have consciousness
right so I would be defined would we
ever be able to define anything about
about computer sure about like Robinson
we are at pretend like I mean if robots
are gonna become very intelligent like
human their favorite develop the product
like new research like the current
experience we have ya know buzz put like
the experience we experience the how it
feels is pretty well defined by new
research is showing that there's a small
part of your brain that conglomerate's
information from other parts of your
brain and creates this experience and
that if
and that if the if that part of your
brain fails which is only a very small
part of your body functions mostly as
normal but you lose consciousness so
that the consciousness is clearly this
very small part of your brain that acts
as a like like you saying this in the
talk is like a CEO it's not like
consciousness is the result of your
entire brain it's a result of a very
specific illusion that happens within
your brain
yeah I understand but to me it seems
like that could be simply be part of
like intelligence like you need to be
that part of your brain to actually like
be able to to compute yes I understand
but what the point is like you can cut
out your vision system in your brain and
you'll be just as conscious and you can
cut out your fu consciousness system and
you'll be great at seeing things still
but you won't be conscious anymore the
experience of consciousness happens on a
specific part of your brain of plenty
but we also refer leave we always refer
to consciousness
remember those two things seem tightly
linked as well right like when you're
unconscious
we don't have memory of things but
things still occurred to you but it's
but there's a difference between so
according to some research when you are
really really drunk it's not that you
lose memory but it's that you are not
conscious right that you lose the
ability to store memories right so
wasn't happening that's different right
why
I mean being that were using the word
different here is it but screwy there's
a difference between experiencing
something and forgetting it and never
experiencing at all but not to you know
not to you awareness raised
consciousness yeah
yeah yeah
all right then I gotta top the last week
but what was like regarding
consciousness right does it make sense
to think about consciousness as like a
Unitarian thing like consciousness seems
like a property of an individual but
what is it really like an individual
that has consciousness or consciousness
is something that is actually a surprise
across several like intelligent
individual like what like clearly like
if you lose our we are still like the
same person you can say we're same
consciousness remains then if you lose a
certain thing eventually like part of
your brain and maybe you lose
consciousness required what define
myself Italian conscious this is the
classic like split brain argument right
there's like these people who they cut
their brains in half and then both their
brain halves are still conscious but
have no means of communication
you have to conscious then you have to
conscious brains within your brain
so we're there to conscious brains to
start with like this is something that
happens in dream so I think I told you
guys already but like sometimes like you
are in a dream and you dream about
somebody telling a joke to you and you
laugh at the end of the joke but it's a
brain chip off yeah no yeah you're
definitely not consciously simulating
the joke it's simply it's by different
part of your brain
yes I know there's not reasonable and so
I think there is one
I think conscious probably stays in one
part and the other part of the box like
oh yeah this is there is a lot of
research pointing that this is true that
this is like so there is actually two
specific parts that cause consciousness
one in the central every hemisphere
which is why it seems that if you split
your brain you can have two fully
conscious individuals inside your head
but then there must be a third that can
for instance
well this is the interesting part the
researcher that they're completely
independent and conscious but somehow
can create the illusion of cooperation
just sometimes one we just help they
individually make decisions and the
other half has the illusion that they
were complicit in the decision he has to
rule they come to hemispheres control
completely different parts of your body
and the other half just rationalizes why
that was a good idea this has been
researched extensively it seems like any
stalkers used a lightweight tool or
things that but - there's time -
dictatorships but they must be the they
must counterbalanced and they have the
illusion that they control each other
well should we end it there discover
anything you call it the sample
consciousness I'll do it oh that sounds
legit wouldn't name it something more
fun yeah the back seats are super comfy
thank you for asking you know there are
other questions good we'll see you guys
tomorrow hopefully if it goes by its
spot some huevos we'll uh we'll show you
about it vici scobie's thank you